Yeah.
No,
it's you coming, son.
I need these packages delivered to associates of mine in the city.
I also need you to retrieve a message for me from a pigeon coop.
Not too far from here.
Bye, Benny.
I'm getting done.
Come back here.
When you're finished.
There are some things we need to discuss and please my son.
Stay out of trouble.
Yeah.
Time
for this.
Hey.
Yeah.
Quiet,
but
no
shame.
What?
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
You're Johnny's kid.
No video.
Tha he just happens to look exactly like the man.
Give it here.
Don't worry, boy.
We're not contagious.
Least I'm not.
Yeah,
it is.
Yeah.
Here, Over here.
I have a delivery from love on the lavatory.
Yes.
Were you followed?
No.
Why would I be followed?
Give me the package.
Tell your father that they're moving tonight.
He should as well.
Who's moving?
What's going on here?
Wait, Come back.
Explain yourself.
A week from this year
has pushed the price.
No, no.
With
stop there.
Right?
Yeah.
No,
that is exploding.
No.
Yeah.
I'm assuming
good.
What?
Father
Federico.
He said it's you.
Thank God.
What happened?
Where is everyone?
They took your father and brothers to the Palazzo Della Signoria prison.
My mother.
My sister.
Claudia.
Are you all right?
Yes, but Mother, she's in shock.
They
when she resisted image.
It's not safe here.
Is there someplace you can take them?
Yes, Yes.
To my sister's.
Good.
Do that.
Meantime, I'll go see my father.
Be careful, Miss.
A radio.
The guards were looking for you as well.
Yeah,
Yeah.
No
many.
Do you think,
right?
No.
You?
The station.
Yeah.
Within the hour.
No,
no.
Would the wind messages left?
He's got my people.
The butcher, please.
Something that gets under way.
We are fine.
What?
No.
Yeah, right.
No,
Booth.
What?
But
yes.
Yeah.
According
Okay.
What?
I'm not supposed to be here.
Only allowed up here,
two
not to, you know, get off So easy.
What?
No!
Release me.
You
do not you stop me.
But I got back from me.
Oh,
not you.
D'oh!
Oh, your breath!
Yeah,
yeah,
Thanks.
Okay,
it's you,
Father.
What's happened?
Took a bit of a beating, but I'm all right.
What of your mother and sister safe now?
Ananta took Yes.
Wait movies.
What happened?
Not the way it did not soon.
It doesn't matter now.
What do you mean, explain?
There's no time.
Listen closely.
Returned to the house in my office is a hidden door.
Used your talent to find it beyond lies.
Just take everything you find inside.
Much of it may seem strange to you, but all of it is important.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Good.
Among the contents is a letter and with it some documents.
I need you to take these documents to me.
Sarah Beth.
He was with me in the office this morning.
Confalonieri, Remember the police Tell me what's happening.
But the party behind this there was a note for you.
He said go into go now.
No
people.
The City Guard is recruiting volunteers for the road patrols and cities.
Why serve with mercenary?
You're right.
You have troubles.
I know a mice.
Yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Father said there was a door here.
Yeah,
yeah.
Trying to talk her.
Hey, what's with their swords?
Aren't you supposed to arrest me?
No.
Let you what you wanted
for you to die.
Well, that's not going to happen.
Why don't we explore other options?
No other options.
Yeah.
What
regional?
I know this from Maestro Corsini.
Let go treatment with the least
No Fine.
May fortune smile upon you Always
shame you would be like that Dough They're gone.
Yeah,
okay.
It's your Dettori.
What are you doing here at this hour?
It's I don't wait, Child.
Take a breath.
Collect your thoughts.
My father and brothers have been imprisoned.
I was told to bring you this.
Uh
I see now it's a misunderstanding at you.
I'll clear everything up.
How?
The documents you've given me contain evidence of a conspiracy
against your family and against the city.
I present these papers that they're hearing in the morning and they will be released.
Thank you, Senor.
Of course, my child.
Do you need a place to stay?
You're more than welcome here.
No grass here.
I'll meet you at the piazza.
Don't worry, it's you.
Everything is going to be fine.
Yes.
No,
thank you.
I have just what you need.
Back ups.
They will not be looking for trouble.
I guess it's no table worrying thing again.
Yeah,
okay.
Yeah.
No.
Do you require medical issues?
You would say I have quite a lot, so
No.
Yeah.
He hasn't come to the attention of the scythe.
I have been timing the cities of release for sport while not illegal.
Say remember, it is only a divertimento.
Someone breaks a leg.
Com wants members provide.
Effective only following you.
Bye.
No.
Which one?
Bye,
Bonnie.
Toy.
You and your accomplices stand accused off the crime of treason.
Have you any evidence to counter this child?
Yes.
The documents that were delivered for you last night.
I'm afraid I know nothing of these doctors.
He's laying
to get closer.
In the absence of any compelling evidence to the contrary.
I am foul.
We announce you, you,
you and your collaborators.
I'm here to buy Santa
Day.
You take one of them.
You may take our lives this way.
Have yours in return.
I swear way.
Hey,
the boy.
He's one of them.
I'll kill you for what you done.
But,
boy,
No.
Hey,
Okay,
I've got little request for you.
I've identified several strange markings that I've discovered right across a Renaissance Italy.
Now, I don't know what they're doing there, but I want you to help me find out Rebecca has marked their general location in the database with an EI icon.
And she's made them glow as well.
Keep an eye out.
No,
it's you.
Thank God.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
I couldn't stop them on net.
I tried, I swear.
But there were so many guards.
Please come with me.
We need to get you after streets.
One of my mother and sister.
They're safe.
I'll bring you to them.
No, It's too dangerous for us to travel together.
Tell me where to go and I'll meet you there.
My sister's house, Just north of the wall.
I'm on my way.
Wait.
They say he's dying
there.
No.
What?
No, No.
You will persist.
The demonstration Once again.
Yeah.
What
Your problem.
Latching?
No.
Okay,
boy.
Yeah.
What?
I mean no harm to anyone.
Yeah.
Okay.
No.
Opened in 14.
65 La Rosa Cota.
The plucked rose quickly became essential to Florentine life.
The women there were known for being upper class.
They were educated in poetry and the arts as well as sexual intercourse.
It was not rare to see members of the same Iorio at La Rosa, Cota and even on occasion, a Medici
E
What?
That's one of the symbols.
What's it mean?
It must be there for a reason.
Can you take a closer look?
Hey, try using eagle vision.
I've got all day.
Wait, That's not possible.
This can't be.
Well, not that's computer code.
Let me compile it.
Oh, shit.
In an encrypted file
uploaded to my computer Maastricht encryption.
I can't.
It's only compatible with the animus itself.
Uploaded to Desmond, then I believe this.
Hello?
This's
they call me subject 16.
Listen, I don't have much time.
There's something I have to show you.
Way Have been lied to this whole time.
Everything we know, Everything we've been brought up to believe it's wrong.
Okay.
Um I've uploaded the evidence file that proves it all, but I've split it into 20 pieces and loved each with a ko Can't be too careful, Queen Isabella?
No, not her.
Uh uh.
What century is it?
Oh, you never mind.
I've hidden the code to the first file inside this programme.
Find it, find them all.
And along the way, you'll begin to see
what the hell?
How did this get inside of animus?
Oh, oh, the memory core we transferred sixteen's memory data from upstair go into the Animas two point.
Oh, He must have hacked the machine when Vidic left him alone between sessions.
Hold on.
Wait a second.
The signs on the walls and Mr Go The ones written in blood.
These were close.
He was telling us to look for them inside the animals.
Yeah.
No,
No.
Okay.
Has he been drinking?
I think we have the wrong building.
No, this is it.
It is a pleasure to make your acquaintance misdirect.
Annette speaks quite highly of you.
I can see why.
I appreciate the kind words Madonna programme called me Power.
Thank you for offering your home to my family power.
It was the least I could do.
You must be tired.
Perhaps you don't know Gradski can't stay.
Why?
Where are you going?
Who kill their toe?
A Bertie.
I understand your desire for vengeance.
But the gun Fallon era is a powerful man.
You are not a killer.
It spare me the lecture.
But I can make you one.
Where are you going?
To teach me how to kill.
I'm not.
I'm going to teach you how to survive.
Come
Discretion is paramount in my profession.
We must walk the streets freely.
Scene.
But Nancy, you two must learn to blend like us and become one with the city's crowds.
My girls will show you how
we'll take good care of you.
No way.
What
trouble?
Chicken
The plant world.
Tough.
Okay,
well, how Who's got a Sharpie?
Yeah.
Hey,
another cell,
just Yeah.
Finding clubs?
No.
Another four?
Then now that you've learned to blend, I'll show you how to use it for more than just moving around.
Let's teach you how to steer.
Once you've stolen from someone else, you mustn't linger.
No money.
All right.
Work with them on your own.
Drinking your magic.
I'm a gonna.
You can go now goes way have to So you He's cute.
Now that you have learned how to approach the enemy, we need to find you a suitable weapon.
What would you have me use?
Ah, but you already have the answer.
Hey, my father's blade.
Embrace her.
Did you get them
by using the same skills I've just taught you?
It's not exactly a working condition.
I assume you're familiar with Leonardo da Vinci.
Si.
That was a painter factor into this.
He's far more than that.
Bringing the pieces you'll see
before I go.
One last question, If I may?
Of course.
Why have you given your age so readily to me, stranger?
I too know betrayal.
Yeah.
I don't go southern cities.
Okay.
What?
I don't know
that
suspecting impurities in the booth.
Stop
with the wind.
Matches left.
He's got it by people of butchers, please.
For procession gets under way.
It will be a fine if not
what
I'm.
What do they cut?
Looks like.
Yeah.
My God has his minus
you.
Yeah.
Okay.
I may be a bit disorganised, but I do know my sweet, They're with me.
I mean,
Leonardo DaVinci opened his own studio after completing his apprenticeship.
Tovar Okeyo.
One of the most successful Florentine artists of the day.
Between 14 76 and 14 81 Leonardo probably continued to collaborate with rodeo, although no one is quite sure what he was working on.
In 14 81 he was given his first commissioned by the monks of San Donato.
A scope ito to paint the adoration of the major in Tru da Vinci style.
He began the painting but never finished it.
Oh, it's the auditory.
I didn't expect to see you again.
What?
With all that's happened,
where are my manners?
Welcome back
Now How can I be of service?
I was hoping you could repair something of mine.
Of course.
Come this way.
Pack your teacher.
Look at you.
Let me clear a space.
All right, let's see it.
Assen 18
I don't know.
It's you.
Despite its age, construction is rather advanced.
I've never seen anything quite like it.
I'm afraid there's not much I can do without the original plants with this Piace.
Wait, wait, wait
what you're doing?
But the contents of this page are encrypted.
But if my theory is correct based on these sketches it may very well it may very well What?
Please sit down.
Out of the way.
Remarkable!
If we transpose the letters and then select every third
No,
there it's finished,
Huh?
What's finished?
The blade.
I managed to the code that parchment of yours.
It showed me exactly what to do.
Now all that's left is to remove your ring finger.
Really?
I'm sorry, but this is how it must be done.
The blade is designed to ensure the commitment of whoever wields it.
Benny,
do it quickly.
I was only having fun.
It's the blade once required to sacrifice.
It's been modified.
You can keep your finger.
Incredible.
Yes, it is.
Tell me, do you have other pages like this?
I'm sorry.
Only the one.
Listen, if you ever do happen across another one of these, please bring it to me.
You have my word.
And thank you for fixing this by order of the Florentine guard.
Open this door.
Just a moment.
Wait here.
Are you Leonardo da Vinci?
How may I be of service?
I need you to answer some questions.
Certainly.
What?
What seems to be the trouble?
A witness claims to have seen you consorting with an enemy of the city.
What?
Me?
Consorting!
Preposterous.
When was the last time you saw or spoke with HBO?
Auditory.
Who known far your finito Donta.
We know you were close with the funny.
Yeah, Perhaps this will help to clear your head.
Ready to talk?
What about now?
Tell me what I want to know and we can end this.
Uh,
no,
thanks.
Uh,
yeah.
Got CSU.
Sorry about that.
And I've got a custom to their abuses.
What of the body?
Bring it inside and put it with the others.
Others.
The city gives them to me for research.
Thank you.
What?
This?
Yeah.
No.
And
over there.
See?
Like it never happened.
Thank you, Leonardo.
Everything.
Any time.
And remember, if you find more off the strange pages, bring them to me.
Should they contain new designs?
I will upgrade your blade as well.
Of course, now I really should be getting back to power for Julie.
Your humanity.
But
what?
What?
But you guys?
Prostitution was one of the most popular occupations for Renaissance women whose only other options in most cases were staying with their families are living in a convent.
Italian society supported prostitution and many brothels were regulated by the government.
At the end of the 15th century, City started to pass laws against prostitution.
Forcing court is ins to wear specific outfits and separating them from respected society.
Date of birth 14 57.
Profession.
Servant.
The auditory families live in servant.
Annetta had one of the few respectable jobs allowed to lower class Renaissance women.
Rich families seldom had more than one or two servants.
Most were young, sometimes Children.
Many hope their masters would help raise their standing, but usually turnover was rapid.
Ultimately, very little is known about Annette.
His life.
She passed on without making a mark on history.
Date of birth.
14 38 Profession.
Madame of La Rosa, Cota There isn't much information about pal in the history books, but the Florentine archives reveal that she was orphaned at age eight when her parents were killed at sea.
Left with a choice between joining a nunnery and prostitution, she began a life on the streets.
At 16, she vanishes from the records on Ly to reappear at age 20 when she was arrested for murdering a city guard.
On an interesting note, Giovanni Auditory represented her in court, winning the case on a self defence plea released from prison.
Pallor went on to start her own brothel to protect many other unfortunate women of the street.
Okay, are no phoney can be designed.
The Palazzo Della Signoria, also known as the Palazzo Vecchio, in 12 99 for the rulers of Florence, the senorita, the Signoria was made up of nine members, or priori, selected by the city's guilds two from each district and a gone polonia of justice.
Members were supposed to be chosen by lot.
But once the Medici family took power on Lee, their friends seemed to end up in the drawing government by the people.
Right.
Interesting fact.
The tower in front is off centre because it was incorporated into the palazzo from an earlier structure.
It contains two small cells, one of which was used to imprison Cosimo de Medici.
Okay,
this document is meant to serve as a record of all I've learned over the past few weeks in the event that I am silenced and prevented from sharing it with you myself.
Understand?
First, that the Duke of Milan's murder was no mere political manoeuvre.
Rather, it has been a piece of a conspiracy that reaches far beyond forensic accounting members in Roma, Venezia and Fort Lee to name but a few cities attached to this note is a list, or rather, the start of one of those I know to be guilty.
Its contents are by no means complete, but I intend to rectify that shortly.
I can, however, say with certainty that the Potsie family is involved.
We must move quickly to question Francesco before he buys his freedom from prison.
Doing so will surely have more names to the list.
I already have my suspicions as to who these men are.
Given that their deeds barrel the hallmarks of an old enemy.
I fear they
the note abruptly ends here.
Giovanni must have had to stop and hide it when the guards showed up to arrest him.